http://www.murdermysterygames.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy  Who we areOur website address is: https://www.murdermysterygames.co.ukOur physical address is 57 The Fairway, Ruislip, London HA4 0SP, UKOur contact details are on this page.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.MediaIf you upload images to this website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsOur site does not currently have a Contact Form with which to gather information about you.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWe use Google Analytics software to collect information about how you use our site. We do this to help make sure the site is meeting the needs of its users and to help us make improvements, for example improving site search.Google Analytics stores information about:the pages you visit on our sitehow long you spend on each pagehow you got to the sitewhat you click on while you’re visiting the siteThe Analytics software does not collect or store your personal information (for example your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.Who we share your data withWhen you buy a game from us, we receive your payment via Paypal or (for our Murder in the Red Room game) Stripe. You can find Paypal's Privacy Policy here. With Paypal, we use Mal's ecommerce to process your order. You can find its Privacy Policy here.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.We keep customer purchase records for as long as needed to assist with any follow-up enquiries. We would not expect this period to exceed ten years.What rights you have over your dataYou have the right to request:information about how your personal data is processeda copy of that personal datathat anything inaccurate in your personal data is corrected immediatelyYou can also:raise an objection about how your personal data is processedrequest that your personal data is erased if there is no longer a justification for itask that the processing of your personal data is restricted in certain circumstancesIf you have any of these requests, get in contact with us.Where we send your dataWe do not sell or rent your data to third parties and we do not share it with third parties for marketing purposes.Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.We design, build and run our site to make sure that your data is as safe as possible at every stage, both while it’s processed and when it’s stored.The personal data we have is unlikely ever to be sent by us outside the European Economic Area (EEA). If this ever does happen, all appropriate technical and legal safeguards will be put in place to ensure that you are afforded the same level of protection as within the EEA.Our contact informationPlease feel free to contact our Data Protection Officer (DPO) if you:have any questions about anything in this documentthink that your personal data has been misused or mishandledData Protection Officeremail:  mmgames[put @ here]mayhem.org.ukMurder Mystery Games57 The FairwayRuislipLondonHA4 0SPAdditional informationHow we protect your dataWe do all we can to keep your data secure. We have systems and processes in place to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure of your data – for example, by using varying levels of encryption.We also make sure that any third parties that we deal with keep all personal data they process on our behalf secure.
